Misaka Mikoto, aka Shocker,
ranked third among espers in the Academy City.
（上条(かみじょう)）
学園都市３位の超能力者
“ビリビリ”こと 御坂美琴(みさか みこと)
She's another one of my acquaintances from before I lost my memories.
記憶を失う前の
俺の知り合いらしい
更に 突然現れた瓜二(うりふた)つの妹
And now, a sister who's a spitting image of her, suddenly appears.
この２人に振り回される
私こと 上条当麻(とうま)
Being taken for a ride by these two, I, Kamijyo Touma...
...had not yet noticed it then...
そのとき
俺は まだ気づいてなかった
...noticed the significance of her sister's existence...
この妹の存在が 何を意味するかを
～♪
#11 Sisters
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
…んだ？　その逃げ腰は
Why're you running?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
愉快にケツ振りやがって
誘ってんのか？
Flashing your buttocks so joyfully at me like that...
You leading me on or something?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
問題です
この俺 アクセラレータは…
Now, question.
What am I, the Accelerator...
果たして
何をやっているでしょう？
...doing exactly?
（御坂妹）反射
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）残念！
"Reflecting".
Sorry, that's not quite the true nature of my skill.
惜しいけど
俺の本質とは違うんだよね
The answer is "vector change".
答えは ベクトル変換
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
運動量　熱量　電気量
Momentum, heat, electric charge...
All kinds of "vectors" can be changed with just the touch of my skin.
あらゆるベクトルは
俺の皮膚に触れただけで変更可能
I do have it set on "reflect" as default, though.
デフォじゃ
反射に設定してあるけどな
Now, time for the consolation prize question.
それでは 敗者復活戦の問題です
I am now touching the flow of blood.
俺は今 血液の流れに触れている
これを逆流させると 人間の体は
どうなっちまうでしょうか？
If I reversed the direction of the flow,
what would happen to a human's body?
ハハッ…
正解者には 安らかな…
A correct answer and you will be given a peaceful... slumber...
眠りを
（上条）
ありゃ？
Huh?
There, there.
それにしても
あいつ どこ行ったんだ？
Really, where did she go?
It... can't... be...
（上条）
御坂？
（警備員(アンチスキル)Ａ）
君… ちょっと 君
Hey.
Hey, you.
（警備員Ａ）
もしよければ
現場に同行してもらいたいんだが
We'd like to ask you to come with us to the scene, if it's okay with you.
You think you can do that?
お願いできるかな？
行きます
I will.
（警備員Ｂ）おい 君！
（上条）えっ えっ？
Hey!
Is something wrong?
（警備員Ａ）
どうかしたのか？
The body was supposed to be... here...
あっ いや ここに
死体があったはずなんですけど
（警備員Ａ）うん？　おい
（警備員Ｂ）ああ
Hey.
Okay.
君 ここには何も…
There's nothing here, kid.
（上条）ホントに…
（警備員たち）うん？
Someone... Someone really died here...
ホントに人が死んでたんです
What's going on?
（上条）
どうなってるんだ…
What's going on here?
どうなってるんだよ くそ！
Damn it!
（警備員Ａ）
あっ 君！
Hey!
How is this possible?
（上条）
どういうことだ？
申し訳ありません　作業を終えたら
そちらへ戻る予定だったのですが
"Forgive me."
"It was my intention to return once I was done with the operation," apologizes MISAKA first.
…と
ミサカは初めに謝罪しておきます
Huh, wait.
お… おい ちょっと待て
お前は御坂妹でいいんだよな？
You're Misaka's sister, right?
ちくしょう… 結局 何だったんだ
Damn it, what was all that in the end?
悪い　今の今まで―
Sorry, I just... thought you were dead all this time...
お前が死んじまったんじゃないかと
思ってたんだ
良かった　何ともないみたいだし
Thank God... and it looks like you're all right...
ミサカは きちんと死亡しましたよ
…と ミサカは報告します
"MISAKA did actually die," reports MISAKA.
お… お前…
What... are you carrying?
一体 なに抱えてんだ？
念のため パスの確認を取ります
…と ミサカは有言実行します
"For security purposes, I am confirming the 'password' with you," as MISAKA proceeds.
（御坂妹）
ＺＸＣ７４１
ＡＳＤ８５２ＱＷＥ９６３
"ZXC741ASD852QWE963," tests MISAKA you.
…と ミサカは あなたに試します
Wh...at?
なに？
今のパスをデコードできない時点で
"Not being able to decode the password shows that you are not related to the experiment," confirms MISAKA.
あなたは
実験の関係者ではなさそうですね
…と ミサカは確認します
その寝袋に入っているのは…
The thing inside your bag is...
（御坂妹Ａ）“妹達(シスターズ)”ですよ
（上条）ハッ…
"Sisters," answers MISAKA.
（御坂妹Ａ）
…と ミサカは答えます
（御坂妹Ｂ）
黒猫を
置き去りにしたことについては―
"I apologize for leaving the black cat behind," says MISAKA.
謝罪します
…と ミサカは告げます
"However, I could not involve an animal in this unnecessary conflict," explains MISAKA.
（御坂妹Ｃ）
ですが 無用な争いに―
動物を巻き込むことは
気が引けました
…と ミサカは弁解します
（御坂妹Ｄ）
どうやら 本実験のせいで―
"It seems I have given you unnecessary worries from this experiment," apologizes MISAKA.
無用な心配を
かけてしまったようですね
…と ミサカは謝罪します
"However, you need not worry."
（御坂妹Ｅ）
しかし 心配なさらずとも…
（御坂妹Ｆ）通報したのも…
（御坂妹Ｇ）あなたということに
"I assume you were the one that called the police."
"Every MISAKA here is MISAKA."
（御坂妹）
ここにいるミサカは
全てミサカですと
（上条）
何だ？　これ
What... is this...
"The MISAKA that you have been in touch with is Serial Number 10032. This MISAKA."
あなたが
今日まで接してきたミサカは―
シリアルナンバー10032
つまり このミサカです
"MISAKA uses the ability to control electricity, and links our brain waves together."
ミサカは電気を操る能力を応用し
互いの脳波をリンクさせています
"The other MISAKA simply share MISAKA-10032's memories," explains MISAKA even further.
ほかのミサカは 10032の記憶を
共有させているにすぎません
…と ミサカは追加説明します
Who are you?
お前は誰なんだ？
"Somatic cell clones, mass produced for military use,"
（御坂10032）
学園都市で
７人しか存在しないレベル５
"that use Misaka Mikoto Oneesama, one of only seven Level 5s in the Academy City, as the original model."
御坂美琴お姉様の
量産軍用モデルとして作られた―
体細胞クローン “妹達(シスターズ)”ですよ
"Sisters," answers MISAKA.
（御坂10032）
…と ミサカは答えます
What are you doing?
お前は何をやってるんだ？
"A simple experiment," answers MISAKA.
ただの実験ですよ
…と ミサカは答えます
詳細は機密事項となっているため
説明できませんが
"I am not permitted to explain details as it is classified information,"
"but this is not an incident," defends MISAKA.
とにかく事件性はありません
…と ミサカは弁明します
"I apologize once more for involving you in this experiment," as MISAKA lowers her head.
本実験に
あなたを巻き込んでしまったことは
重ねて謝罪しましょう
…と ミサカは頭を下げます
"Please care for the cat."
では 猫をお願いします
Experiment?
実験？　軍用？
Military use?
Why are you wasting your time here?!
（美琴）
あんた！　一体 どうして
こんな所でブラブラしてんのよ？
"MISAKA's-"
（御坂妹）ミサカは…
（美琴）いいから
It's okay!
Just come.
来なさい
もしかして あいつは
このことを知ってたっていうのか？
Don't tell me...
...she knew about all this?
Itadakimasu!
（小萌(こもえ)）いただきま～す！
（姫神(ひめがみ)）…ます
-masu.
Since Himegami-chan is a guest, start with this.
（小萌）
姫神ちゃんは居候さんなので
まずは これです
（小萌）
さあ！　先生のために―
Now, cook these pieces of meat for Sensei.
ちゃっちゃと
お肉 焼いちゃってください
（姫神）
うん　けど―
But...
その前に 学園都市であった
怖い話をひとつ
Before that, let me tell a scary tale about the Academy City.
Sensei won't be crying just from seven mystery stories.
先生は 七不思議程度で
泣き出すマネはしないのです
A component of the char from the yakiniku meat...
（姫神）
焼き肉のお焦げに含まれる成分…
It actually leads to cancer.
実は 発がん性物質
Th-That kind of actual scary fact doesn't fit summer story telling!
ちょ… そんな本当に怖い話は
夏の風物詩じゃないです
Is this your plan to lower my appetite so that you can monopolize all the meat for yourself, Himegami-chan?
こっちの食欲削って お肉を
独占する計画ですか？　姫神ちゃん
（ドアチャイム）
うん？　お客さんですね
Another guest.
It's probably someone with a circulation notice, but could you go handle him appropriately, Himegami-chan?
回覧板だと思いますが
姫神ちゃん
丁寧に対応してあげてください
In the meantime, Sensei will be cooking some meat and...
先生は
その間に 勝手にお肉焼いて…
...eating up, okay?
勝手に食べちゃいますよ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
お… おなかへ…
I'm star-
Hmm, who was that?
あれ？　誰だったんですか？
No, nothing was there.
いえ　別に何でも
At least... At least feed him... feed Sphinx...
せめて… せめて この子だけでも…
スフィンクスだけでも
ア～ン…
Touma just hasn't come back yet,
so I thought I'd die from starvation.
当麻が
いつまでも帰ってこないから
飢えて 死ぬかと思ったんだよ
プハ～ッ…
Don't worry!
大丈夫！
１人や２人 増えたくらいで…
It's just one or two more people.
This deluxe yakiniku set,
plentiful in quantity, can handle that.
（小萌）
量に不満が残る―
豪華絢爛(けんらん)焼き肉セットでは
ないのです
わあ！　お肉 お肉 お肉！
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Next stop, "Seventh school district -
Tokiwadai Middle School Student Dormitory".
（ｱﾅｳﾝｽ）
次は
第７学区 常盤台(ときわだい)中学 学生寮前
Misaka Mikoto
208号室
Room 208.
（上条）
えっと…
I see her, then what?
あいつに会って
どうしようっていうんだよ？
Am I going to ask about the details of a horrifying experiment where people get killed easily?
人ひとり平気で殺すほどの―
おぞましい実験の内容を
聞こうってのか？
（インターホンに出る音）
（黒子(くろこ)）はい
Yes?
あっ… あ～ えっと… 御坂か？
Misaka?
This is Kamijyo.
上条だけど
Ahh... Kamijyo-san, you say?
（黒子）
はぁ… 上条さんですの？
あっ… ああ　すいません
部屋の番号を間違えてしまって
Ah, sorry! I got the wrong room number.
No, no, don't worry.
（黒子）いえいえ　大丈夫ですの
（上条）うん？
（黒子）
私 お姉様とは相部屋ですから
I am Oneesama's roommate.
I see.
そうだったんですか
Yes, indeed.
（黒子）
そうだったんですよ オホホホッ…
Wait, where have I heard this voice before?
待てよ
この声 どこかで聞いた気が…
（黒子）
はて… どこかで
お聞きしたような声ですわね
That's funny, I've heard your voice somewhere before...
AHHHHH!!!
あなた！　昨日
お姉様と密会されてた方ですね？
You! You're the guy that rendez-vous-ed with Oneesama yesterday, aren't you?!
キーッ！　お姉様に何の用ですの？
What do you need from Oneesama?
It's nothing major, but I-
あっ いや 大した用じゃ…
How rather suspicious of you to be coming all the way here for "nothing major".
（黒子）
大したことじゃないのに
わざわざ来るなんて 怪しいですわ
If she's not there, then it's okay.
いや… いないんなら いいんだ
Oneesama has not returned yet.
（黒子）
お姉様は
まだ戻っておられませんわ
If you need to see her, I recommend you come in and wait for her.
ご用がおありでしたら 中に入って
待つことをオススメしますの
Room 208.
（上条）
208号室… ここだ
It's here.
Come in.
（黒子）
どうぞ　鍵はかかっていませんので
The door isn't locked.
失礼します…
Coming in...
So it was you, after all.
（黒子）
やっぱり あなたでしたのね
Y... You're...
あっ… お前は…
Don't tell me you and Oneesama
committed a mistake afterwards...
（黒子）
まさか
あのあと お姉様と何か過ちを？
ううん！　ないない！　ない！
No, no, no!
フン… でしょうね
I bet you wouldn't.
それに そういう浮いた話を
しに来たわけではないようですし
Besides, it doesn't seem like you're here to talk about such steamy subjects.
If you're going to wait for Oneesama, then take a seat on that bed.
お姉様を待つのでしたら―
そのベッドに
腰かけてくださいですの
Wait, that's kind of rude.
（上条）
いや… マズイだろう さすがに
本人の許可も取らないで
I didn't even get permission from her.
Don't worry.
（黒子）
ご心配なさらずに
そちらが私のベッドです
That's my bed.
えっ？　じゃ そっちが御坂の…
Then that's Misaka's...
What are you doing on someone else's bed?
他人のベッドの上で
何やってんだよ？
What are you, a pervert?
もしかして 変態さんか？
（黒子）
変態とは聞き捨てなりませんの
Calling me a pervert is quite hard to ignore.
There are things that people consider
"this should be acceptable" inside their hearts.
人間 人には言えないものの―
心の中では“こんぐらいＯＫ”と
考えているものです
You know, like playing the recorder that belongs to a girl you like,
ほら　好きな女の子のリコーダーに
口をつけたり
自転車のサドルをパクってきたり
or stealing the person's bike saddle.
（上条）
しねえよ！
I don't do any of that!
Is this the true state of rich girl schools?
…たく
お嬢さま学校の実態ってのは
こんなもんなのか？
あっ そういや お前
御坂と相部屋ってことは同級生か？
Wait, so since you're Misaka's roommate, are you the same school grade as her?
You call her Oneesama, so I thought you were an underclassman.
“お姉様”なんて言ってるから
てっきり 後輩だと思ってたけど
No, no, I am an underclassman.
いえいえ　私 れっきとした
お姉様の後輩ですのよ
I am in a lower school grade, too.
学年も下です
Then, why are...
じゃ なんで…
I had the previous tenant move out, and I moved in.
前任の同居人には
出ていってもらって
私が代わりに入ったんですの
Legally, of course.
あくまで合法的に
Oneesama has a lot of enemies, too.
お姉様も敵が多いですからね
力持つ者の業とはいえ―
Granted, it's the fate of those with power,
but for the person living in the
same room as her to be a traitor,
さすがに
同じ部屋で寝泊まりする人間が―
裏切り者というのは
つらすぎると思いません？
don't you think that's too painful?
And, you must be the gentleman that has been quarreling with Oneesama frequently, right?
それで あなたは
ふだんから お姉様と頻繁に―
いさかいを起こしてる殿方で
よろしいんですの？
Forgive me if I'm mistaken.
違うなら それで かまいませんの
I simply wanted to see the face of the one that has been giving Oneesama support.
お姉様の
支えとなってる方のお顔を―
少しばかり拝見してみたいと
思っただけですから
支え？
Support?
Is she back?
（上条）帰ってきたのか？
（黒子）この足音…
These footsteps...
ハッ… マズイですわ！
This isn't good!
It's the dorm supervisor's inspection time!
寮監の巡回のようです
（上条）えっ？
（黒子）ああ どうしましょう
What should we do?
If they find out that a gentleman is inside a room of Tokiwadai's girls' dormitory...
常盤台の女子寮に―
殿方がいることが知れたら
大変なことに
We're going to teleport outside for a bit, okay?
ちょっと
外にテレポートしてもらいますわよ
How come my power doesn't work on you?!
あなた どうして
私の力が働かないんですの？
いや その… きっと 俺の右手が…
Umm... I'm sure my right hand's the problem...
We have no choice.
（黒子）
ハァ… しかたありませんわ
Go hide under the bed!
ベッドの下にでも
隠れてくださいませ
Ow!
いてっ！
Wait, it's impossible!
ちょっと ムリだって この隙間は…
It's too tight!
Just get in!
（黒子）いいから！
（上条）ンンッ…
狭いんだよ
It's so cramped in here.
（寮監）
白井(しらい)　夕食の時間だ
Shirai, it's time for dinner!
食堂へ集合せよ
Gather in the cafeteria.
うん？　御坂は？
Where's Misaka?
Oneesama's at make-up lessons.
（黒子）
お姉様でしたら 補習ですわ
長引いてらっしゃるのでは？
Maybe it's taking longer.
（寮監）
そういう報告は受けてないが
I did not hear any reports of this.
If she is going to break curfew, then her roommate will also be deducted one point, okay?
もし門限破りなら―
同居人と連帯責任で
原点１と見なすが かまわんか？
Yes, I understand.
（黒子）ええ　もちろんですわ
（寮監）うん
フゥ…
ファスナー？
Zipper?
“妹達(シスターズ)”って…
Sisters... this is...
Level 6?!
“レベル６”？
"From the estimated calculation using Tree Diagram,"
“樹形図の設計者(ツリーダイアグラム)を用いて
予測演算した結果―”
"it has been concluded that only one person can attain the unknown, Level 6."
“絶対能力者 レベル６に
到達できる者は１名のみと判明”
"By preparing special battlefields,"
“特定の戦場を用意し―”
"and by fighting according to the scenario,"
“シナリオどおりに
戦闘を進めることで―”
"his growth will be stimulated by the battlefield..."
“実戦における成長を促し”…
ナメやがって…
This is wrong.
Where... Where is she?
（上条）
どこだ？　どこにいるんだ？
There's no wind, yet the propellers are turning?
（上条）
風が吹いてないのに
プロペラが回ってる
Wind electricity is created from the rotation of the propellers.
風力発電は プロペラを回すことで
電気を発生させる…
Conversely, if electricity is being propagated through them, then the propellers will turn.
逆に 電気を浴びせることで
プロペラは回る
Her body generates voltage every second.
（上条）
あいつの体からは
常に電磁波が出ているはずだ
That means, if I follow those propellers...
ということは
あれを追っていけば…
～♪
Next Episode
（上条）
リポートに書かれていた衝撃の事実
The shocking truth written in the report.
For Misaka, who's shouldering the tragic fate of the Sisters to the point of being crushed, I...
妹たちの残酷な運命を背負って―
押しつぶされそうに
なっている御坂に 俺は…
次回 「絶対能力者(レベル６)」
Next time, "Level 6".
When science and magic cross paths,
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる
this epic will begin!